Guide to the Griffith J. Davis photographs and films, 1946-1991 RL.00292
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Scanned still image negatives, 1946-1949; 342 items 2 boxes
  - Palmer Memorial Institute, Sedalia, North Carolina, 1946-1947; 124 items
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-59 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0061)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-60 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0062)
    - Sewing class gives Henri chance to make dress for chapel fashion revue. She prefers skirts and sweaters to wear around campus., 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-61 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0063)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-62 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0064)
      Palmer Memorial Institute. Sewing class setting.
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-63 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0065)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-64 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0066)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-65 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0067)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-66 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0068)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-67 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0069)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-68 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0070)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-69 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0071)
    - In library, Henri studies English lessons. Every PMI student must pass college entrance exam before graduation., 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-70 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0072)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-71 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0073)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-72 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0074)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-73 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0075)
      Palmer Memorial Institute. Same shot as PMI-70. "In library, Henri studies English lessons. Every PMI student must pass college entrance exam before graduation."
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-74 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0076)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-75 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0077)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-76 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0078)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-77 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0079)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-78 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0080)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-79 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0081)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-80 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0082)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-81 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0083)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-82 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0084)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-83 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0085)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-84 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0086)
      Palmer Memorial Institute. Same shot as PMI-85. "Before girl's dorm, Henri bids her escort goodnight after first big dance while envious lower classmen watch from windows."
    - Before girl's dorm, Henri bids her escort goodnight after first big dance while envious lower classmen watch from windows, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-85 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0087)
      Palmer Memorial Institute. Title transcribed from caption in Ebony magazine.
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-86 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0088)
      Palmer Memorial Institute. Same shot as PMI-87. "Getting ready for annual prom, Henri helps decorate gym…"
    - Getting ready for annual prom, Henri helps decorate gym. Entrance to prom is by invitation of junior class. Ballroom Dancing is taught in special class., 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-87 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0089)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-88 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0090)
      Palmer Memorial Institute. Same general shot as PMI-91.
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-89 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0091)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-90 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0092)
    - Daily personal contact with each student is a must in Dr. Charlotte Hawkins Brown's education formula. In her office (above) she talks over student affairs with senior class president Edward Clark of New York. Each morning at 8:30 chapel service (below) she addresses student body, limited to enrollment of 240., 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-91 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0093)
      Palmer Memorial Institute. Title transcribed from caption in Ebony magazine. The reference to Dr. Hawkins' office indicates an illustration on the article page; this image occurs later in the digital collection sequence.
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-92 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0094)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-93 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0095)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-94 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0096)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-95 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0097)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-96 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0098)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-97 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0099)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-98 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0100)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-99 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0101)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-100 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0102)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-101 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0103)
      Palmer Memorial Institute. Similar shot to PMI-105.
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-102 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0104)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-103 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0105)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-104 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0106)
    - Singing and playing with children in her Canary Cottage, Dr. Brown proves quite active despite her 63 years, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-105 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0107)
      Palmer Memorial Institute. Title transcribed from caption in Ebony magazine article (photocopy in collection folder). Rest of caption reads, "Youngest is 2-year-old grandniece Carol Lane, visiting from Boston. Other three are youngest PMI students who customarily live in the president's home. Palmer age limits are 11 to 18; average is 15. School has one ex-GI in his 20s."
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-106 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0108)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-107 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0109)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-108 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0110)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-109 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0111)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-110 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0112)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-111 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0113)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-112 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0114)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-113 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0115)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-114 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0116)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-115 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0117)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-116 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0118)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-117 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0119)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-118 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0120)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-119 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0121)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-120 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0122)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-121 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0123)
    - No known title, 1946-1947; Original identifier: PMI-122 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0124)
  - Langston Hughes in Atlanta and New York, 1948-1949; 108 items
    Biographical / Historical
    The close friendship between Griff Davis and Harlem Renaissance author Langston Hughes (1902-1967) began in Davis' college days and lasted for decades. They collaborated on journalistic projects, and Davis often accompanied Hughes as his official photographer.
    These photographs, on cellulose nitrate and safety film, were taken by Davis for a photo-essay on Langston Hughes in Ebony magazine, and document Hughes in New York City in his apartment and backstage with theater and musical performers, and in Atlanta, visiting with students and faculty at Atlanta University and Morehouse College. Some of these images also appeared in biographies and other publications about Langston Hughes. Positive scans of the negative images are available for viewing through the links with each entry.
    - Front door panel at 20 East 127th Street decorated for Christmas holidays, 1948-1949; Original identifier: LH-1 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0125)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. This New York City building is where Langston Hughes lived.
    - Front door panel at 20 East 127th Street decorated for Christmas holidays, 1948-1949; Original identifier: LH-2 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0126)
    - Front door panel at 20 East 127th Street decorated for Christmas holidays, 1948-1949; Original identifier: LH-3 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0127)
    - Front door panel at 20 East 127th Street decorated for Christmas holidays, 1948-1949; Original identifier: LH-4 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0128)
    - Langston Hughes visits Negro-owned Hopkins Book Corner, bookstore on Auburn Avenue in Northeast Atlanta, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-5 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0129)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Caption continues: "L to R on picture is LH, Jacob Anderson, Sr. (one of three owners) and Ellington, store manager."
    - Langston Hughes visits Negro-owned Hopkins Book Corner, bookstore on Auburn Avenue in Northeast Atlanta, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-6 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0130)
    - No known title, 1947; Original identifier: LH-7 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0131)
      Langston Hughes at Atlanta University (extrapolated from similar images).
    - No known title, 1947; Original identifier: LH-8 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0132)
    - Langston Hughes teaching class at Atlanta University, 1947; Original identifier: LH-9 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0133)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Caption continues: "Students came from colleges in A.U. Center - Spelman College, Morehouse College, Clark College, Norris Brown College, etc." This image also appears with the same title in The Life of Langston Hughes by Arnold Rampersad.
    - No known title, 1947; Original identifier: LH-10 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0134)
      Langston Hughes at reception, Atlanta University (extrapolated by library staff from similar images).
    - Exhibit in Atlanta University Library on Langston Hughes upon his arrival on campus for 1947 semester as Guest Professor, Original identifier: LH-11 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0135)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection.
    - Exhibit in Atlanta University Library on Langston Hughes upon his arrival on campus for 1947 semester as Guest Professor, Original identifier: LH-12 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0136)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-13 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0137)
      Langston Hughes, seated, posed portrait.
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-14 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0138)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-15 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0139)
      Langston Hughes portrait, at typewriter.
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-16 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0140)
      Langston Hughes, posed portrait by window.
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-17 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0141)
    - Langston Hughes and Dr. Nathaniel Tillman, Sr., head of Atlanta University English Department, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-91 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0142)
      Title extrapolated by library staff from Griff Davis title for LH-91, on title list in collection. Caption continues: "Statue of W.E.B. DuBois, former Atlanta University professor."
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-19 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0143)
      Langston Hughes.
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-20 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0144)
      Langston Hughes at typewriter.
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-21 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0145)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-22 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0146)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-23 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0147)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-24 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0148)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-25 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0149)
      Langston Hughes. Same setting as LH-27, Yates and Milton drugstore.
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-26 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0150)
    - Langston Hughes at Yates and Milton drugstore, an off campus hangout for students, with A.U., Morehouse, and Spelman students, 1947; Original identifier: LH-27 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0151)
    - Langston Hughes with Atlanta public school students, 1947; Original identifier: LH-28 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0152)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Also appears in The Life of Langston Hughes by Arnold Rampersad, "Negro History Week, Atlanta, 1947." Photocopy is in collection folder of materials on Langston Hughes in the Photographs and Papers series.
    - Langston Hughes with students at David T. Howard Jr. High School in Atlanta, Principal Charles Gideons and Teacher Edith Wimbush Bowens, 1947; Original identifier: LH-29 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0153)
    - Langston Hughes at class registration, Atlanta University, 1947; Original identifier: LH-30 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0154)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Caption continues: "During registration students sign up for his class."
    - Juanita Toomer, English professor at Spelman College, shakes hands with Arna Bontemps in Spring 1947 after his presentation in Langston Hughes course, Original identifier: LH-31 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0155)
    - Arna Bontemps appears as guest lecturer in Langston Hughes class, Atlanta University, 1947; Original identifier: LH-32 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0156)
    - Artist Aaron Douglas and Arna Bontemps of Fisk University with Langston Hughes after class at Atlanta University, 1947; Original identifier: LH-33 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0157)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-34 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0158)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-35 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0159)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-36 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0160)
    - Reception for Langston Hughes at Atlanta University, 1947; Original identifier: LH-37 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0161)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Caption continues: "LH with Atlanta University President Rufus E. Clement and A.U. students."
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-38 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0162)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-39 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0163)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-40 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0164)
    - Langston Hughes speaking at Morehouse College Founders Day banquet in February 1947, Original identifier: LH-41 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0165)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Caption continues: "President Benjamin E. Mays (with hand to mouth). Looks like Martin Luther King, Sr. next to Mays."
    - Langston Hughes conducting Creative Writing class at Atlanta University, 1947; Original identifier: LH-42 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0166)
    - Langston Hughes with Rev. William Holmes Border (r) and Charles Gideons, principal of the Atlanta public school, David T. Howard Jr. High School, 1947; Original identifier: LH-43 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0167)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-44 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0168)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-45 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0169)
    - Langston Hughes portrait used on cover of pocketbook edition of The Ways of White Folks, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-46 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0170)
    - No known title, circa 1947; Original identifier: LH-47 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0171)
    - Langston Hughes and Morehouse student and photographer Griffith J. Davis, 1948; Original identifier: LH-48 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0172)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Caption continues: "They later collaborated on some picture articles for EBONY magazine e.g. Atlanta in January 1948. Taken in Atlanta at Langston Hughes's faculty apartment." Library staff note: The student is not evident in this image; perhaps he or she took the photograph.
    - Langston Hughes in his combination bedroom-office at 20 E. 127th, New York City with secretary Nate White, 1949; Original identifier: LH-49 (frames 19, 20, 21) (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0173)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. This New York City building is where Langston Hughes lived. Image consists of three frames on a 35 mm negative film strip.
    - Langston Hughes at his usual work table sitting before his upright manual typewriter, 1949; Original identifier: LH-50 (frames 8, 9, 10) (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0174)
      LH-50 (9). Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Image consists of three frames on a 35 mm negative film strip. One of the images appears in The Life of Langston Hughes by Arnold Rampersad, with caption reading "Later that day."
    - Langston Hughes secretary Nate White brings key morning mail to Langston Hughes while he is still in bed (probably 2pm), 1949; Original identifier: LH-51 (17,18) (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0175)
      LH-51 (frame 17) Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Image consists of two frames on a 35 mm negative film strip. Image of LH in bed, alone (frame 18), appears in The Life of Langston Hughes by Arnold Rampersad; the caption reads: "About noon one day in 1949."
    - No known title, circa 1948; Original identifier: LH-52 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0176)
    - No known title, 1949; Original identifier: LH-53 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0177)
      Langston Hughes, backstage.
    - Langston Hughes backstage at Broadway presentation of "A Streetcar Named Desire" with Edna Harris (?) doing interviews for Ebony article, 1949; Original identifier: LH-54 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0178)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Question mark is Griff Davis's. According to another photograph caption in the Ebony article of March 1949 (photocopy in collection folder), an actress in "Streetcar Named Desire" is Edna Thomas.
    - Langston Hughes backstage in New York City, 1949; Original identifier: LH-55 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0179)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. The caption continues: "See Ebony article, circa 1950 for identification of artists."
    - Langston Hughes with Dizzy Gillespie backstage at Apollo Theater, in New York City, 1949; Original identifier: LH-56 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0180)
    - Langston Hughes backstage with Nellie Lutcher (?) in New York City, 1949; Original identifier: LH-57 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0181)
      Caption transcribed, including question mark, from Griff Davis title list in collection folder. Caption continues: "Printed in EBONY 'backstage' article." Nellie Lutcher (1912-2007) was a jazz and R&B singer and pianist. Hughes appears in mirror.
    - Langston Hughes in his bedroom/workroom at 20 E. 127th, New York City, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-58 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0182)
      Title extrapolated by library staff from Griff Davis title list in collection. This New York City building is where Langston Hughes lived.
    - Langston Hughes in his bedroom/workroom at 20 E. 127th, New York City, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-59 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0183)
    - Langston Hughes in his bedroom/workroom at 20 E. 127th, New York City, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-60 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0184)
    - Langston Hughes in his bedroom/workroom at 20 E. 127th, New York City, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-61 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0185)
    - Langston Hughes in his bedroom/workroom at 20 E. 127th, New York City, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-62 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0186)
    - Langston Hughes in his bedroom/workroom at 20 E. 127th, New York City, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-63 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0187)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-64 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0188)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-65 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0189)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-66 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0190)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-67 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0191)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-68 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0192)
    - Langston Hughes with student assistants in faculty apartment at Atlanta University. Prepares for academic convocation., circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-69 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0193)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-70 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0194)
      Title extrapolated by library staff from Griff Davis title list in collection. Arna Bontemps [American poet] and Langston Hughes.
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-71 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0195)
    - Arna Bontemps and Langston Hughes photo used on book jacket of their anthology of Negro writers and in Hughes-Bontemps "letters" book, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-72 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0196)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. In 1980, Arna Bontemps, an American poet, published collected letters exchanged with Langston Hughes from the 1920s to the 1960s, selected and edited by Charles H. Nichols.
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-73 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0197)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-74 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0198)
    - Langston Hughes typewriter being repaired by Atlanta University maintenance repairman - Atlanta, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-75 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0199)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-76 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0200)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-77 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0201)
      Langston Hughes. Same setting as LH-79, working with student assistants.
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-78 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0202)
    - Student assistants hired by Langston Hughes at Atlanta University working on his personal projects, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-79 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0203)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-80 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0204)